https://www10.MCADcafe.com/policy/privacy_policy.php

News»
Daily News
Corporate Newsletters
Subscribe
Submit New
Events»
Event Calendar
Submit Events
Purchase Webinar Listing
Editorial»
Jobs
Companies»
Company Directory
Product Catalog
Submit
Videos»
Videos
Submit New Video
Submit New YouTube Video
Downloads»
RSS
Advertise»
MCADCafe Media Kit
Banner Ad Specifications
eMail Blast Specifications
Inquire
Internet Business Systems, Inc.
Privacy Policy
Internet Business Systems, Inc. (IBS) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. (Our privacy applies to all our web sites: www.edacafe.com, www.mcadcafe.com, www.giscafe.com, www.aeccafe.com, www.pcbcafe.com, www.dcccafe.com, www.nanotechcafe.com, and www.careerscafe.com.)
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how IBS treats personal information that IBS collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that IBS does not own or control, or to people that IBS does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
General
IBS collects personal information when you register to download software, presentations, and papers, when you register to use our DACafe mail, and when you register for sweepstakes or other promotions or services.
When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and other contact information. Once you register with IBS and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.
IBS automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP Address, IBS cookie information, and the page you request.
IBS uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
IBS will not monitor or disclose any private e-mail message or address information unless required by law, regulation, court order, or legitimate administrative purpose. Any personally identifiable information that you provide will only be used by IBS and certain business partners in order to provide you with a more customized and efficient service. You may receive program information and updates from IBS periodically, and have the right and ability to opt out of any communications not directly related to the IBS service you are utilizing.
IBS does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with IBS under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help IBS communicate with you about offers from IBS and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of IBS's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
We transfer information about you if IBS is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, IBS will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
IBS may display targeted advertisements based on personal information.
IBS does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
IBS advertisers include companies who cater to the needs of the industry you are in.
For example, in the EDA space (www.edacafe.com) our advertisers include primarily EDA software and hardware manufacturers.
Cookies
IBS may set and access IBS cookies on your computer.
Advertisers or other companies do not have access to IBS's cookies.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
General
You can edit your IBS Account Information at any time by clicking here to contact us.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the IBS service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and IBS Newsletters that are considered part of your IBS account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
You can delete your IBS newsletter account by visiting http://www10.MCADCafe.com/nl/newsletter_subscribe.php where "MCADCafe" is the site you receive your newsletter from.
For example, if you receive your newsletter from EDACafe.com then the deletion url would be http://www10.edacafe.com/nl/newsletter_subscribe.php.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
IBS may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your IBS account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:
Internet Business Systems, Inc.
Privacy Policy Issues
Phone: +1 (408) 882-6554
Contact Us
© 2020 Internet Business Systems, Inc.
670 Aberdeen Way, Milpitas, CA 95035
+1 (408) 882-6554 — Contact Us, or visit our other sites:
Privacy PolicyAdvertise
